it's fun being a comedian it's a lot of
fun it's a lot of work you know I know
it's crazy
it used to think it was work before but
now it's a lot of work because you got
to write jokes that's easy right kind of
but it's all the social media people
it's just too much man is and I you know
most people are great online but he's
got some crazies out there some people
are really cool and I don't need
everyone to like me I'm not about that I
don't need you to like me I'm from
Brooklyn I'm good right but if you don't
like me I don't need you to tell me you
said I'm saying like just don't like me
over there but everyone's got you know
what you know when the best time to be
performer was it was the 80s that was
cuz it was like there was TV but you
could there was separation you know like
I say you hate it Lionel Richie in the
80s you had no way of telling Lionel
Richie that you hated him
you had to eat that like that was just
something you have to distill what maybe
you could tell your friends I heard you
monitor see I think all right all right
you couldn't just call that already up
and be like hello like you couldn't do
that that was not an option
in fact the only way you could tell
Lionel Richie that you hated him in the
80s was to buy a ticket to a Lionel
Richie show a good ticket first ten rows
they could hear you right here to drop
some serious 80s coin like thirty five
dollars you to pay $35
so give me the first 10 rows you got
there earlier you were stretching you're
getting ready like when he comes out
i'ma say hey chi'lan I'mI'm so excited
I'm a mess of the whole show he's gonna
know I hate him he's gonna cry then it
came out he went right to some Commodore
songs
you forgot his with the Commodores he
was like well some of the conference
stuff is actually pretty cool though I
like you're like okay after the comment
of stuff I'm gonna say I hate you a lot
of Richard did he did the song with
Kenny Rogers you're like oh I like that
song to actually write Frankie did he
think we are the world was like our man
it was less way he wrote we are the
world man
after this was there they did two other
songs you even know he was there with
Lionel Richie about an hour and a half
in you're like you know what I think I
love Lima Richie actually and and the
problem with the Internet is that you
can't get kicked off that's the real
issue with it you can't you can do
whatever you want today come back do it
again as a society that's not how we set
this thing up the whole power we have to
make everyone act right is we can
ostracize you we can send you to jail
right we can see you to Australia like
wherever we need to send you even in
this room we can kick you out okay
Internet you come back the next day same
problem with homeless people you can't
really tell homeless people what to do
you really can't because they're they're
already outside do you understand
you can't kick them more outside is what
I'm saying like how do you threaten them
right you keep acting up imma get you in
the apartment I swear I'll pay you first
and last month win play games with me
and see if I'm gonna set you up in an
apartment
subscribe to drive our comedy for even
more of the world's largest collection
of clean comedy